hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨， Spring 粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of swing tips in this
在这里的秋千技巧的分期付款
installment we're gonna look at the
分期付款，我们将看看
Apache Geo project and its integration
Apache Geo项目及其集成
through the spring data geode projects
通过 spring data geode项目
now spring data geode supports Apache
现在Spring Data Geode支持Apache
geode and you might have otherwise heard
乔德，你可能已经听说过
of Apache geode as gem fire right so Jim
Apache geode作为宝石之火，所以Jim
fire is actually a product a product
火实际上是一种产品
that is existed for the better part of
存在的大部分
two decades it's been around for a long
已有二十年了
time and it predates the the obviously
时间，它早于
predates pivotal it predates the the
早于关键
spring team's time at VMware but it was
Spring 团队在VMware的时间，但是
acquired around the time of the
在
acquisition of the spring source by
通过获取Spring 源
VMware and it's it's one of those things
VMware，这就是其中之一
that if you've if you've got a use case
如果你有一个用例
that served by this product then you
该产品提供的产品，然后您
absolutely know about this technology
绝对了解这项技术
it's something that you will probably
这是你可能会做的事
have looked into and more than likely
已经研究了并且很有可能
used right it's why those one of those
使用正确，这就是为什么其中之一
best kept secrets it's um it's the thing
最好保密的东西
that just people have used without
只是人们已经习惯了
having to be advertised to right we've
必须刊登广告，我们已经
we've had so much success with people
我们在与人之间取得了很大的成功
finding it just sort of naturally
自然地发现它
organically they're looking to solve a
他们正在有机地寻求解决
certain problem and that problem that
某个问题和那个问题
domain is distributed data grid
域是分布式数据网格
technology right they want something
技术对他们想要的东西
that's able to act as a giant Ram cloud
可以充当巨大的Ram云
but you know replicated or partition
但您知道复制或分区
across a giant cluster of nodes that
跨越庞大的节点集群
supports for example caching of data
支持例如数据缓存
from fast lightning quick access for
从快速闪电快速访问
continuous queries for you know for
您知道的连续查询
analytics and for when replication that
分析以及何时复制
is to say I want to take data from one
就是说我想从一个
data center and then replicate the data
数据中心，然后复制数据
if necessary to two other data centers
如有必要，另两个数据中心
worldwide right so get a consistent view
全球范围内正确的观点
of the data and this is particularly
的数据，尤其是
valuable this horizontal scalability and
这种水平可伸缩性和
this infinite sort of replicability
这种无限的可复制性
across different nodes this is
跨不同的节点，这是
particularly useful in the cloud native
在云原生环境中特别有用
world recall that of course Netflix when
世界当然回想起Netflix
they made their journey in a cloud
他们在云端旅行
native you know circa 2009 they talked
你说的大约2009年的当地人
about their movement away from
关于他们远离的运动
traditional storage technologies like
传统的存储技术，例如
sequel sequel based databases to to a
基于续集的续集数据库
distributed technology like Cassandra
像Cassandra这样的分布式技术
something that has no single point of
没有一点的东西
failure
失败
geode
乔德
very much in that same fashion now when
现在非常以同样的方式
I say deed I am referring to Jim fire
我说行为是指吉姆·火灾
Jim fire is a product but we have since
Jim fire是产品，但自
open-source all that so a bit for bit
开源一点点
all the interesting stuff that you want
您想要的所有有趣的东西
and that you're gonna want to use is an
而您要使用的是
Apache deal and so while we while we're
阿帕奇交易，所以当我们
going to see different API is today that
今天要看到不同的API
refer in in in in in some cases to to
在某些情况下指
you know calm that Jim fire no that
你知道吉姆开枪没有
fundamentally substantially it is an
从根本上说，这是一个
open source technology called Apache geo
称为Apache geo的开源技术
and really they're interchangeable
实际上，它们是可互换的
at this juncture at this point right and
此时此刻，正确的是
this is a it's been a long journey you
这是一段漫长的旅程
know we've had a live had a long journey
知道我们过了一段漫长的旅程
to see this product open-source but
看这个产品开源
pivotal as part of its commitment to
作为其承诺的一部分至关重要
open source we open source to all of our
开源我们向所有我们开源
data technologies a few years ago so
几年前的数据技术
green plum and and you know our saw are
青梅，你知道我们看到的是
working in Jim fire and all these things
在吉姆之火和所有这些事情中工作
these Big Data technologies became open
这些大数据技术变得开放
source so we're going to look at that
来源，所以我们要看一下
technology today now I am I'm just gonna
今天的技术，我就是我
go ahead and say I'm really sorry that
继续说我很抱歉
this hasn't been done before I'm sorry
对不起，这还没有完成
that we haven't had a spring tip on this
对此我们还没有Spring 提示
before
之前
Jim fire and geode are to me some of the
Jim fire和geode对我来说是
most interesting technologies under the
最有趣的技术
Sun they are amazingly powerful these
太阳，它们异常强大
are technologies that as I say we don't
正如我所说，我们不会
really have to advertise right and I
真的必须做广告，我
recall at VMware we had customers that
回想在VMware，我们有客户
would come to us and say wow you know we
会来找我们说哇你知道我们
just paid you know some obscene number
刚付钱就知道一些淫秽的数字
that can only ever be justified by um
只能由um来证明
that can only ever be just to buy it
那只能是买它而已
through justified through some sort of
通过某种理由
golf game right they pay for some sort
高尔夫游戏，他们付某种钱
of terrible price for this golf game and
这个高尔夫比赛的可怕价格
they'd end up with these extra licenses
他们最终将获得这些额外的许可证
of coherence right it wasn't like that
连贯的权利不是那样的
they it wasn't like they wanted it it's
他们不是像他们想要的那样
just what they had right and and they'd
他们所拥有的权利，他们会
come to us and say we really want to use
来找我们说我们真的很想使用
gem fire right that's the technology
宝石之火就是技术
that actually does what coheres does but
确实做到了，但是
it actually does it it actually it has
它确实做到了
these features and it's been battle
这些功能，这是战斗
tested right Fortune 100 companies large
经过测试的《财富》 100强公司
chunk of them are using Jim fire it's
他们中的很大一部分正在使用Jim fire
one of those things that even after we
甚至在我们之后
open sourced it were able to to to
开源它能够
satisfy customers because they're
让客户满意，因为他们
they're continually happy with this
他们对此一直感到满意
technology so this is one of those
技术，这就是其中之一
things where it's just been really
真的是真的
really good right it's just been really
真的很好，真的
good for
对...有好处
a long time now and we haven't had to do
很长一段时间了，我们不必做
any kind of traditional marketing to to
任何形式的传统营销
support that um it's also one of those
支持那个，它也是其中之一
things where because it works so nicely
因为它很好用的地方
with spring and it's been with within
Spring 来了
the spring ecosystem and because we've
Spring 的生态系统，因为我们已经
had people working on it for so long it
有人花了很长时间
benefits right it benefits from spring
受益于 Spring
simplicity and spring to benefits from
简约和 Spring 从中受益
its power its flexibility and so the
它的力量，灵活性等等
journey with with gem fire the
与宝石之火的旅程
integration with Jim Fire has come a
与Jim Fire的整合已经
long way my goodness I remember when it
我的天哪，我记得很长一段时间
was first integrated into the spring
第一次融入 Spring
family spring source Engineer Causton
家庭Spring 源工程师Causton
Lau was working on it right he was one
Lau正在努力地工作，他当时还是一个
of the if you look at the oldest code in
如果您查看的是最早的代码
the spring dad it read his project
Spring 爸爸，他读了他的项目
you'll see his name in there as well I
你也会在那里看到他的名字
mean he's he's a and he's also in spring
意思是他是他，他也在 Spring
framework itself right he's one of the
框架本身就是他之一
legends of the original sort of motley
原始杂色的传说
crew that that formed spring source and
组成Spring 源的船员
so so he having those excellent
所以他有那些优秀的
technical chops was was working on on
技术印章正在研究中
the Jim for integration and you know
整合的吉姆，你知道
let's just be brutally honest here the
让我们在这里说实话
integration the possible integrations
整合可能的整合
that we we could do with spring struck
我们可以用 Spring 来袭
up 2010 took up 2010 or 11 we're not as
最多2010年占用了2010年或11年，我们没有
elegant as what we can do today because
像我们今天可以做的那样优雅
the product itself has become much more
产品本身已经变得越来越多
developer centric it has historically
历史上以开发者为中心
been a data analysts platform it's been
曾经是数据分析师平台
a technology geared for data sort of
专门用于数据排序的技术
people right people working in an
人们正确的人在
organization that care about data
关心数据的组织
provenance and they care about data
起源，他们关心数据
analytics and warehousing all these kind
所有这些类型的分析和仓储
of use cases and so for it to now be
用例，因此现在
able to bridge that gap to sit
能够弥合差距坐
comfortably in both worlds to have
两个世界都舒适地拥有
tooling and to have integrations
工具和集成
available to both sides of the
可供双方使用
proverbial house that's a rare
众所周知的房子
distinction right a lot of technologies
区分很多技术
focus and and if and and even then don't
专注于，如果，甚至甚至不
necessarily succeed on one side of the
一定会成功的一方面
house so I think this is a really
房子，所以我认为这是一个非常
interesting technology now people use
人们现在使用的有趣技术
geode which is as I say a giant
就像我所说的巨人
distributed RAM cloud basically it's a
分布式RAM云基本上是
data grid we call it they use it for a
数据网格，我们称其为
lot of different use cases they use it
他们使用它的很多不同的用例
for for for buffering so I've used
用于缓冲，所以我用了
you know I've used other technologies
你知道我用过其他技术
like coherence before in production
像生产前的连贯性
right and and and this serves a lot of
对，这对很多人都有好处
the same use cases this serves a lot of
相同的用例可以满足很多
the same use cases um suppose I have a
相同的用例，假设我有一个
whole bunch of data that I want to to
我想要的全部数据
buffer I'm gonna write it to a back-end
缓冲区我要写到后端
data store but that that back that back
数据存储，但那又回来了
in data store is slow
数据存储中的速度很慢
that is to say it can't accept writes as
那就是说它不能接受写为
fast as I can as I can contribute them I
尽我所能尽我所能
can use this this data grid to buffer
可以使用此数据网格来缓冲
those rights to to absorb them and then
吸收他们的权利，然后
as possible write them to the B to the
尽可能将它们写到B到
data store that's behind the data grid
数据网格后面的数据存储
we call that right behind that in that
我们称其为
interaction that message exchange
交互即消息交换
protocol that's called right behind if
被称为if的协议
you want to read data suppose you um
您想读取数据，假设您
suppose you wanted to read data from
假设您想从中读取数据
something that is slow right
缓慢的东西吧
you read data from backing data store
您从备份数据存储中读取数据
but it's slow but you want to make sure
但是很慢，但是你要确保
that subsequent reads are fast right so
随后的读取很快，所以
this is called read-through you read you
这称为通读，即读即读
read through the cache the cache can
通过高速缓存读取高速缓存可以
then be programmed to read from the
然后进行编程以从
original source thing it'll look up the
原始来源的东西会查找
record it'll resolve the resulting
记录它会解决结果
record and it'll return the record but
记录，它将返回记录，但是
it'll then cache that record so that
然后它将缓存该记录，以便
subsequent reads for the same key in
随后读取相同的键
this data grid will result in the cached
该数据网格将导致缓存
object and you can do things like
对象，您可以做类似的事情
expiration of values you can say I want
您可以说我想要的价值到期
to read through but it says if this has
通读，但它说如果有
been idle and nobody's read it or
闲着，没人读
whatever for X number of minutes or
无论X分钟的时间，还是
hours or a second to whatever then go
几小时或一秒钟
ahead and expire it that way the next
前进并以这种方式到期，下一个
time I read it I'll be I'll be forced to
每当我读到它，我就会被强迫
resolve the original object again and
再次解析原始对象，然后
I'll get a fresh read so you can do also
我将重新阅读，您也可以这样做
to be very interesting things you know
成为非常有趣的事情
these are classic cache patterns and
这些是经典的缓存模式，
they're certainly I think common and
他们当然是我的共同点，
then indeed you'll see that spring has a
那么确实您会看到 Spring 有一个
cache manager integration and so while
缓存管理器集成等等
I'd love to talk about the cache manager
我很想谈谈缓存管理器
integration you know something when we
整合，当我们知道
looked at when we looked at for example
例如当我们看时
the Redis support and spring data Redis
Redis支持和spring数据Redis
what I'd love to
我想要的
look at that integration today we're
看看今天的整合，我们
gonna focus on some of the more
将专注于更多
interesting features of geode proper I
晶莹剔透的我有趣的特征
don't want to linger on too much on
不想在上面停留太多
these lower level pieces you can
这些较低级别的作品，你可以
absolutely give them to work they're not
绝对给他们工作，他们不是
a big deal but we're gonna focus on some
很大，但是我们要专注于一些
of the new integrations made possible by
新集成的实现
spring data Jim fire or spring data Geo
spring data Jim fire或 spring data Geo
depending on what you want to call it
取决于您要调用的名称
and the spring boot data geode
和Spring Boot数据Geode
integration so that is a bit of a
集成，所以有点
confusing name that is not a library
令人困惑的不是图书馆的名字
that's in spring boot itself it is
那是在 spring boot 本身
instead of spring boot starter that is
而不是Spring 启动启动器
provided by the spring data geode team
由Spring Data Geode团队提供
all right so I'm if if I if I pronounced
好的，如果我说了，我就是
it wrong if I named it incorrectly at
如果我在处错误地命名了它是错误的
least I hope I correctly articulated
至少我希望我能正确表达
what it is and what do you might
这是什么，你可能会做什么
logically expect to find it now in order
逻辑上希望现在能按顺序找到它
to do this we're gonna build a client
为此，我们将建立一个客户
and a service so we'll do that here of
和服务，所以我们将在这里
course and for the moment just for the
当然，目前仅用于
moment there's not really a lot we can
那一刻我们没有太多可以
do here besides generate a new project
除了生成一个新项目，在这里做
we're gonna call this the server
我们将其称为服务器
okay I'm gonna use long buck and when we
好吧，我要花很多钱，当我们
use the latest and greatest to that 101
使用最新和最伟大的101
om4 I'm gonna hit generate and then I'll
om4我要点击“生成”，然后我将
build a client and the same thing and I
建立一个客户，同样的事情，我
hit generate and that's it that's my two
打generate，就是我的两个
dependencies I have my zip file my zip
依赖我有我的zip文件我的zip
files here and so we're gonna start with
文件在这里，所以我们将从
a server and the server is going to be
一台服务器，该服务器将是
as I say um a a thing that will store
正如我所说的，这将存储
data now in in in geode part loss
数据现在在大地测量零件损失中
there's several moving parts to a given
给定有几个运动部分
cluster a server is a thing that stores
集群服务器是要存储的东西
data
数据
it's a node that stores data in a server
它是一个将数据存储在服务器中的节点
you have what are called regions regions
你有所谓的区域区域
are logical partitions of lerna I should
是lerna的逻辑分区，我应该
avoid using the word partitions they're
避免使用分区字
logical chunks of the of the server they
他们的服务器的逻辑块
correspond to maybe a database schema
对应于数据库模式
for example right you might have a
例如，您可能有一个
region called people and inside that
那个叫人的区域
region you have keys and values right
您拥有键和值的区域
it's um it's a it's a map ultimately
嗯，最终是地图
it's a dictionary if you will so you put
这是一本字典，如果你愿意的话
a key in there you can reserve you can
您可以在其中保留一把钥匙
resolve values from those keys what kind
从那些键解析值是什么样的
of keys anything really any complex
的键真的很复杂
object in Java
Java中的对象
anything you want a string that idea you
任何你想要的想法
know a foo a bar whatever you want pride
知道一个foo吧，无论你想要什么骄傲
can be a key and or a value and you can
可以是键或值，您可以
use that to resolve these references our
用它来解决这些参考
servers are not your first
服务器不是您的第一台
sort of contact not your first point of
接触不是您的第一要点
contact with respect to the client so a
与客户联系，因此
kind is a thing that will talk to the
善良的东西会和
cluster and it will resolve data but it
集群，它将解析数据，但是
needs to be dispatched basically there
需要基本上派到那里
needs to be something that will tell it
需要是可以告诉它的东西
where to find that data and so that
在哪里找到这些数据，以便
lives typically in a locator and locator
通常生活在定位器和定位器中
is a a component that you know acts as a
是一个您知道充当的组件
dispatcher as a load balancer and a and
作为负载均衡器的调度程序，以及
a service registry ful tells you where
服务注册中心会告诉您在哪里
to find notes tells the client where to
查找便笺告诉客户在哪里
find nose and it gives it metadata about
找到鼻子，并为其提供有关的元数据
the topology of the cluster itself once
集群本身的拓扑
that's been resolved and typically the
已经解决，通常
client will connect to one of many
客户端将连接到许多
locators right you you will typically
定位器通常会适合您
have at least three locators in the
至少有三个定位器
application once it's resolved one of
解决后的应用程序之一
the locators it'll it'll then find a
定位器会找到一个
node and they'll connect to that node
节点，他们将连接到该节点
and then subsequent incantation
然后随后的咒语
subsequent invocations will work
随后的调用将起作用
directly with the nodes right it'll the
直接与节点对它会
node once connected will give it will
节点一旦连接就会给它
connect to the client to other nodes if
如果连接到客户端到其他节点
it needs to so why do we have three
它需要所以为什么我们有三个
located well that's a good question
位置很好，这是一个好问题
right we have at least three locators so
对，我们至少有三个定位器
think about this a locator is the you
考虑一下这个定位器就是你
know it's the it's the brain for all
知道这是所有人的大脑
first connections for clients so it's
第一次为客户建立联系
pretty important you don't want to lose
很重要，你不想输
this thing in the application when you
当您在应用程序中
need it and so suppose I wanted to
需要它，所以想我想
deploy you know version 1.1 of my
部署您知道我的1.1版
locator code of my locator node and so I
我的定位器节点的定位器代码，所以我
have to take the locator down well of
必须把定位器放好
course I need a backup right and well
我当然需要备份
first of all you want to backup so in
首先要备份
case one Falls you have the backup but
情况一，你有备份，但是
then suppose I want deployed version 1.1
然后假设我要部署1.1版
of the locator of one of the byte of
的以下字节之一的定位符的
warning one of the running instances
警告正在运行的实例之一
well then I have to take that down now
好吧，我现在必须把它记下来
I'm down to one I have one instance and
我只剩下一个实例
so in this case that thing the backup
所以在这种情况下，备份
now needs a backup so it's always good
现在需要备份，所以总是很好
to have three at a minimum you can have
最少要三个
more but there is a there is a useful
更多，但有一个有用的
limit there's not a technological limit
没有技术上的限制
but there is a useful limit because
但是有一个有用的限制，因为
these things are pretty chatty right so
这些东西很健谈，所以
you wanna you you know you'll have a you
你想你知道你会拥有你
know at least three locators and maybe a
至少知道三个定位器，也许
little bit more but after that the cross
多一点，但在那之后十字架
can become a pretty noisy for the
会变得很吵
network so we want to limit that as much
网络，所以我们想尽可能地限制
as possible wherever possible okay now
现在就尽可能
we are going to build an application it
我们将要构建一个应用程序
is going to be a so a locator first of
将会是第一个这样的定位器
all is also a cache server so we're
都是缓存服务器，所以我们
gonna say that this is gonna be a cache
要说这将是一个缓存
server but in order for us to do that of
服务器，但为了我们做到这一点
course we do need to bring in the
当然，我们确实需要引入
requisite dependencies don't we so we
必需的依赖不是我们，所以我们
have a few dependencies that we need to
有一些我们需要的依赖
bring in here I'm just gonna go ahead
带进来，我要继续
and do this manually right now these
并立即手动执行这些操作
checkboxes this these starters are not
这些启动器不是的复选框
reflected in the spring and newtralizer
反映在 Spring 和缓和剂
which is a bit of a pity but there are
有点可惜，但是有
milestones yet so early days and keep in
里程碑，但仍处于初期阶段，并保持不变
mind I did use the one dot o M for
介意我确实使用了一个
support here so spring geode starter and
在这里提供支持，以便 Spring geode入门
org spring framework geode and the
org spring framework geode和
version is going to be 100 M 3 100 M 3
版本将是100 M 3 100 M 3
and the next thing I'm gonna bring in is
我接下来要介绍的是
I've already got Lombok done' so I want
我已经把龙目岛做好了，所以我想
to bring in the spring shell dependency
引入spring shell依赖
here so spring the shell org spring
在这里， Spring ，壳组织 Spring
framework shell and
框架外壳和
that is gonna be pinned at 1.29 oh that
那将被固定在1.29哦
release for now and III hope that in
现在发布，III希望
time this dependency will just be
时间这种依赖将是
provided for me it'll be implied or
提供给我，这将被暗示或
removed or whatever why I did it by the
删除或无论我为什么这样做
start but for now just for our purposes
开始，但现在仅出于我们的目的
here now we'll leave that there
现在在这里，我们将留在那里
all right so there we go there's our
好吧，所以我们去那里是我们的
bare minimum locator of code we're going
我们要去的最低限度的代码定位器
to say that this is a locator
说这是一个定位器
application in order for it to be a
为了使其成为一个应用程序
locator application we need certain
定位器应用程序我们需要确定
things in play as I said first of all it
我首先说过的事情
needs to be a cache server all right so
需要成为缓存服务器，这样
it's a locator is both a node a server
它既是定位器又是服务器的节点
node and this also this other thing
节点，这也是另一件事
called the locator so when I tell it to
叫定位器，所以当我告诉它
basically talk to itself write locators
基本上是自言自语地写定位器
location is equal to 1000 3 3 or 4 and
位置等于1000 3 3或4并且
you're gonna want to remember that
你会想起那个
that's a common common default so just
这是常见的常见默认设置，所以
keep that in mind and then finally we
记住这一点，最后我们
want to create a because there is a
要创建一个，因为有一个
duality here we have we are both a
双重性在这里，我们都是
server and a locator we're going to
服务器和定位器，我们要去
create a configuration class separate
单独创建一个配置类
and apart from our locator class static
除了我们的locator类static
are looking server part you know that
正在寻找服务器部分，您知道
says that class locator good figuration
说，班级定位器很好的形象
and it doesn't need to be that way by
并不需要那样
the way you can you can you can layer
可以的方式可以分层
these you can stack these on top of the
这些你可以将它们堆叠在
spring good application annotation if
Spring 良好的应用程序注释如果
you like right so at an able manager and
你喜欢对，所以在一个干练的经理那里，
start will be equal to true alright so
开始将等于真正的好吧，所以
there we are there's our very very basic
我们在那里，这是我们非常非常基本的
configuration in order for this to work
配置以使其正常工作
we need some configuration we need some
我们需要一些配置我们需要一些
basic properties that we're gonna we're
我们要的基本特性
gonna have in play and so these
会玩，所以这些
properties are not yet in the auto
属性尚未自动
completion so they are bring spring dots
完成，所以他们带来 Spring 点
data dot dem fire cache dot name equals
数据点DEM火缓存点名称等于
random value and string dot data that
随机值和字符串点数据
Jim fire dot cache server dot port
Jim Fire点高速缓存服务器点端口
equals 0 and 0 of course tells it to
等于0，当然0告诉它
find the first unused port and
找到第一个未使用的端口，然后
use that okay so there we go there's our
用那好吧，所以我们去那里是我们的
locator note let's try that we need to
定位符请尝试我们需要
have locators running before we can have
在我们可以拥有定位器之前
a server so this is this is pretty
服务器，所以这是漂亮
straightforward okay
直接好吗
okay what did I do wrong let's see we've
好吧，我做错了什么，让我们看看
got an error of some sort yeah well it
出现某种错误，是的，很好
looks like I what did i do is that one
看起来我在干什么
too many threes that might be yeah
可能是太多的三分球
now what did I do hmm
现在我该怎么做
it is complaining about an unknown host
它抱怨未知的主机
of local host
localhost
alright seems that's up and running
好吧，好像已经启动了
that's good that's as we expected it to
很好，正如我们期望的那样
be now what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
现在我要做的就是我要
build a a server note write an actual
建立一个服务器说明写一个实际的
server a proper server that's
服务器是一个适当的服务器
independent because I and I will have
独立，因为我和我将拥有
many more servers and it will have
更多的服务器，它将有
locators so I'm going to build a new
定位器，所以我要建立一个新的
package here server and this one as you
打包在这里服务器，这与您一样
might imagine this a fair bit simpler
可以想象这会简单一些
because it is a subset of the thing we
因为它是我们事物的一部分
need for the locator at least for now
至少现在需要定位器
so server application voila okay and
这样服务器应用程序就可以了
public static void main string args and
公共静态void主字符串args和
here I'm gonna say spring application
这里我要说 Spring 申请
run server application class args okay
运行服务器应用程序类args可以
very good okay so there's our server
很好，好的，有我们的服务器
application and in order for that to
申请并为此
work of course it needs to be a valid
工作当然必须是有效的
spring boot application like so and
像这样的Spring Boot应用程序和
let's just take advantage of this
让我们利用这个优势
copying and pasting and in order for
复制和粘贴并为了
that to work I think that's it I think
工作，我想就是我想
that's all we need actually I think
这就是我们真正需要的
that's the let me just think about this
这就是让我考虑一下
for a second yeah I mean for now that's
是的，我是说现在
that's probably right okay now we have
大概没关系，现在我们有了
the server and in the server I want to
服务器和我要在服务器中
define a region right and so the region
定义一个正确的区域，因此该区域
I need to define somewhere and I'm gonna
我需要定义一个地方，我要
do that in terms of an entity and an
按照实体和
entity I'll store in a common package
我将存储在通用包装中的实体
and now naturally you could and more you
现在自然可以，而且更多
more commonly would extract this out
更常见的是将其提取出来
into separate common package and create
放入单独的通用包装并创建
an entity of type whatever and I'm going
任何类型的实体，我要去
to store those entities here I'm gonna
将那些实体存储在这里
create a thing of stores temperature
创造存储温度的东西
sensor data right this is a domain very
传感器数据对，这是一个非常领域
much inspired by demos I've seen by a
灵感来自于我所看到的演示
spring data geode lead John bloom and
spring data Geode负责人John Bloom和
and geode subject matter expert luke
和geode主题专家卢克
Shannon so I'm gonna go ahead and just
香农，所以我要继续
borrow or appropriate that that sample
借用或适当使用该样本
because I think it works quite well so
因为我觉得效果很好
suppose you have high speed sensor
假设您有高速传感器
feedback indicating the temperature for
指示温度的反馈
various cities or regions and though in
各个城市或地区，尽管在
the world okay so we're gonna have a
这个世界还好，所以我们要
type here
在此输入
a temperature that is going to store
将要存储的温度
information about guess what temperature
有关猜测温度的信息
readings so of course I'm gonna use
读数，所以我当然会用
Lombok I love lombok it makes my life
龙目岛我爱龙目岛它使我的生活
just that much easier and it's going to
那样容易得多，它将
be an object that's gonna be stored in a
成为要存储在一个对象中的对象
region and that region I'll call timpz
地区和该地区，我将其称为timpz
and I'll have a ID here like that
这样我就有一个ID
private double temperature and private
私人双温和私人
string city all right there we are and
弦城好吧，我们在那里，
ID okay so there's our spring data
ID好的，所以有我们的 spring data
mapped type and I want to tell my server
映射类型，我想告诉我的服务器
application about this thing that we've
关于这个东西的应用
just created so I want to actually I
刚创建，所以我想实际上我
want to include it in the scan of the of
想要将其包括在的扫描中
the code right so I'm gonna include that
代码正确，所以我要包括
plus the actual application itself here
再加上实际的应用程序本身
so I say components can base package
所以我说组件可以基础包装
classes and I'll tell it to find server
类，我将告诉它查找服务器
application class and temperature dot
应用类别和温度点
class okay voila so they're just
上课好吧，瞧，他们只是
overwriting spring boots default
覆盖 spring boot 默认
components can behavior so as to have it
组件可以行为以便拥有它
pick it up that that component so now we
拿起那个组件，所以现在我们
could we start the locator I'm happy
我们可以启动我很高兴的定位器吗
with that let's go ahead and now restart
这样，让我们​​继续，现在重新启动
the server after we change our
更改服务器后的服务器
configuration so server very cool
配置，使服务器非常酷
apply go
申请去
all right we've got a locator and a
好吧，我们有一个定位器和一个
server up and running so that's very
服务器启动并运行，因此非常
good now we're gonna come back to this
好，现在我们要回到这个
right we will certainly come back to
对，我们一定会回到
this but for now let's go ahead and
现在，让我们继续前进，
should you know make progress on our on
您是否知道我们的进步
our client and in the client code we
我们的客户和客户代码中
have a let's see here a visit file CD
让我们在这里看看访问文件CD
plant we've got that ueo client done zip
植物，我们已经完成了ueo客户的zip
alright and in the client code you know
好的，在客户端代码中，您知道
we're gonna do the same thing we have a
我们将做同样的事情
the common dependencies of loop so we'll
循环的常见依赖关系，所以我们将
copy do some copy pasta there copy and
复制做一些复制面食复制和
paste those dependencies from here and
从这里粘贴那些依赖项并
paste those into pom that XML alright
将它们粘贴到XML正确的pom中
very good so that saves us quite a quite
非常好，这样可以为我们节省很多
a bit of setup in ceremony which I'm
我在仪式上做了一些设置
happy about because I loathe ceremony
因为我讨厌仪式而高兴
and in the client let's get rid of these
在客户端让我们摆脱这些
packages just as before well have a set
像以前一样有一套
of package here for for client and then
的包装在这里供客户使用，然后
there in will create a class called
在那里将创建一个名为
client application and our class is a
客户应用程序，我们的课程是
spring good application string arguments
Spring 良好的应用程序字符串参数
spring application run
Spring 申请运行
plant application class ARBs all right
工厂应用程序类ARB可以
very good so there's that and our client
很好，就是这样，我们的客户
application is gonna do a few things
应用程序会做一些事情
it's gonna actually connect to the data
它实际上将连接到数据
store it's gonna write data to the
存储它会写数据到
database for us now in order for it to
现在为我们提供数据库
do that it's going to also have that
做到这一点也将有
common type right so we're gonna we're
正确的普通类型，所以我们要
gonna have it talk to our region so we
要和我们地区谈谈，所以我们
need that same type this is where would
需要使用相同的类型
be useful to extract this out into a
将其提取到一个有用的
separate jar and then share that across
分开的罐子，然后分享给大家
but for our purposes just to keep things
但是为了我们的目的只是为了保留东西
as simple as possible we're gonna just
尽可能简单，我们只是
copy and paste okay this is not
复制并粘贴好吧，这不是
necessarily what you'd do in a typical
一定是你在典型情况下会做的
ocation but again for our purposes and
职业，但再次出于我们的目的
there are two components here this is
这里有两个部分
the server that actually stores the data
实际存储数据的服务器
so you're not gonna that's gonna be a
所以你不会那样的
separate thing right that's gonna be
单独的事情将是
independent of what we have here and
不依赖于我们在这里和
then in the client application here we
然后在客户端应用程序中，我们
want to build an application that will
想要构建一个应用程序
take the data that it sees and turn that
拿走它看到的数据
data into regions I'm gonna say at
数据进入我要说的区域
enable entity define regions base
启用实体定义区域基础
package class will include temperature
包装类别将包括温度
class and we're going to attend able
上课，我们要参加
cluster definitions right there we go so
集群定义就在那里
alright and it will cluster
好吧，它将群集
configuration
组态
I knew that look weird alright so we've
我知道那看起来很奇怪，所以我们
got this now now we've got our our basic
现在有了这个，我们有了基本的
client application and this is just this
客户应用程序，这就是这个
this part super familiar right this is a
这部分超级熟悉的权利，这是一个
this is I think for most of us our happy
这是我认为对于我们大多数人来说，我们幸福
path right this is like the thing we're
正确的道路就像我们
all used to know to do it we take a type
所有以前都知道要做的事，我们采取一种
I'm gonna put a repository out of it
我要放一个仓库
extend the crud repository here it's
在这里扩展crud存储库
gonna manage instances of entities herbs
要管理实体草药的实例
have temperature whose primary keys of
具有其主键为
type long we'll save that and then we're
键入长，我们将保存该内容，然后
going to create a thing that writes data
要创建一个写数据的东西
to the database like so implements
像这样实现到数据库
application runner it's gonna be a thing
应用程序运行程序将是一件事情
that gets initialized when the
当
application starts up so application
应用程序启动，因此应用程序
ready event and there we're gonna be
准备好的活动，我们将会
giving a call back when the application
申请时回电
starts up so implement those methods
启动，因此实现那些方法
and we'll say add component I'm sorry
我们会说添加组件，对不起
application listener all right everybody
大家好，应用程序监听器
okay there's our event and what we're
好的，有我们的活动，我们有什么
going to do is we're going to when the
我们要做的是
application starts up write data to the
应用程序启动将数据写入
database so I'm gonna use the repository
数据库，所以我要使用存储库
that we've just created that spring data
我们刚刚创建了那个 spring data
is gonna create for it's going to inject
将为它注入而创建
that repository here to to to do that
该存储库要做的是
you know creation reading updating and
你知道创作阅读更新和
deleting in data so we're gonna do that
删除数据，以便我们做
here in the the in application starts up
在这里in应用程序启动
so that's just create a very simple flow
所以这只是创建一个非常简单的流程
I'm gonna say okay find everything when
我要说好吧，什么时候找到
the application starts up and then for
该应用程序启动，然后
each one of those I'm gonna call this
我要称呼它的每个人
temperature a positive delete right like
将正温度删除，例如
so passing in T right okay so in that of
所以传入T吧，好吧，
course there's a method reference just
当然有方法参考
waiting to be used there we go so now
等待在那里使用，我们现在就去
we've reset everything if we have any
如果有的话，我们将重置所有内容
data it's all gone now and then finally
数据全部消失了，然后终于
what I do want to write some data to the
我想写一些数据到
database so I'm gonna insert some data
数据库，所以我要插入一些数据
insert and then we're gonna say for int
插入，然后我们要说int
I 0 eyes left then int max or I suppose
我左0眼然后是int max或我想
it's a in to start let's do offset okay
这是一个开始，让我们抵消吧
wouldn't start from a random offset so
不会从随机偏移开始
we're gonna say math dot you know what
我们要说数学点，你知道吗
do random dot next int and this the int
在next int和int之间做随机点
will be oh let's say a thousand int
会是一千个整数
random offset okay
随机偏移可以吗
let's say random offset I plus plus so
假设随机偏移量我加上加上所以
I'll be plus 100 it's that way it's
我会加100就是这样
guaranteed to be at least 100 okay and
保证至少100正常，并且
once that's done we're going to write
一旦完成，我们将要写
data to the database okay and here I'm
数据到数据库好了，我在这里
just gonna create a little method
只是要创建一个小方法
that'll actually handle the insert for
实际上将处理插入
me
我
okay now insert will
好吧，现在插入
code now and that insert it's gonna just
现在输入代码，然后插入
be fairly straightforward you know code
相当简单，您知道代码
what I'm saying let's create a new
我说的是让我们创建一个新的
temperature temperature you know I don't
你知道我不知道
actually have a sensor to connect my
实际上有一个传感器来连接我的
application to so we'll do it the
应用程序，所以我们将
old-fashioned way right to the data
老式的数据访问方式
manually okay so new random dot next
手动好吧，所以下一个新的随机点
long and the next value that we want is
长，我们想要的下一个值是
a temperature so new random dot next
温度那么新的随机点
double and then we need a random City
加倍，然后我们需要一个随机城市
and of course I'll extract that out into
我当然会把它提取出来
a separate method make it easier and so
单独的方法使其更容易，因此
string cities and Fran Cisco I'm in
弦城市和我在的Fran Cisco
beautiful Toronto at the moment as I
当下我美丽的多伦多
write this sand Ramon and Gabriel Los
写这个沙子拉蒙和加布里埃尔·洛斯
Angeles Paris Shanghai Tokyo Seoul Cairo
安吉利斯巴黎上海东京首尔开罗
etc okay so I've got now a bunch of
等等好，所以我现在有一堆
cities let's go ahead and create an
城市让我们继续前进，创造一个
array divide that there and now for each
数组将其划分为现在和每个
city for string city in cities I'm gonna
我要去的城市中的弦城市
write the data to the database all right
可以将数据写入数据库
sorry know for each city I want to
抱歉，我想要的每个城市
return a random one don't I so I've got
我随机返回一个，所以我有
a hard core list I'm gonna say return
我要说的硬核名单
new random
新随机
dot next int city's dot length int index
点next int城市的点长int索引
okay there's my index I'm gonna say
好吧，我要说的是我的索引
returning cities index there we go okay
返回城市指数，我们可以
so I'm gonna return I'm just gonna
所以我要回来我只是要
generate a random one that's bounded by
产生一个随机的
the number of elements in the array and
数组中元素的数量和
I'll return the random offset into that
我将随机偏移量返回
array that's bounded by that so it's not
受其限制的数组，因此不是
gonna be any more than that and then
会不止于此，然后
I'll use that to create this temperature
我将用它来创建这个温度
object and you'll notice that I've got a
对象，您会注意到我有一个
number of different cities that start
开始的不同城市数
with Sam right so we'll use that later
和山姆说对了，所以我们以后再用
on tour to demonstrate some analytics
巡回演出以演示一些分析
capabilities okay so now we've got that
功能还可以，所以现在我们有了
we've got the raw one now let's save it
我们现在有原始的，让我们保存它
so this stuck temperature repository at
所以这个卡在温度仓库
save passing in temp alright so there's
保存传递的温度好吧，所以
the saved record very straightforward if
保存的记录非常简单，如果
you've ever used spring data and now I
你曾经用过Spring 数据，现在我
want to say this temperature repository
想说这个温度库
that find my ID saved
找到我的ID已保存
doc can get ID you know want to say if
doc可以获取您想说是否的ID
it's if it exists by ID and then I want
如果它通过ID存在，那么我要
to map it I say give me the the ID of
映射它，我说给我的ID
course so temperature get ID and then or
当然，温度会获得ID，然后或
else no okay so there's that ID and what
否则不行，所以有那个ID和什么
I want to confirm is that the ID that
我想确认的是
I've returned from my cache matches
我已经从缓存匹配中返回
right is true let's try that this is a
没错，让我们尝试这是一个
Spring Framework class good for
Spring Framework类适合
production code good for you know DBC
对您熟悉的生产代码DBC
design by contract kind of assertions
按合同设计断言
I'm going to say is true equals is equal
我要说的是真的等于等于
to say is equal to saved get ID so I
说等于保存的获取ID，所以我
should be able to write the data in and
应该能够在其中写入数据
then pull it right back out okay so
然后把它拉回来就好了，所以
let's see should exist in the database
让我们看看数据库中应该存在
all right there we go so there's my
好吧，我们去，所以有我的
updated code right cool okay so now we
更新代码很酷，所以现在我们
now written any number of records here
现在在这里写了许多记录
right randomly when the application
正确的时候申请
starts up we're running data to the
启动我们正在运行数据到
database now I think that's actually a
现在我认为这实际上是一个数据库
pretty good first start let's go ahead
很好的开始，让我们继续
and just see that that works now before
并看到它现在可以工作了
we do that let's connect using G fish so
我们这样做，让我们使用G鱼连接
I'm here in this column here in the
我在此专栏中
Patchi geo distribution directory and
Patchi地理发行目录和
I've got a I mean the the bin directory
我有一个我的意思是bin目录
and I've got a number of shell utilities
而且我有很多shell实用程序
including something called G G fish this
包括一些叫做GG鱼的东西
is a gem fire or a suppose geode shell
是宝石之火或假想的外壳
right within G fish you've got a lot of
在G鱼中，您有很多
capabilities here so I can say okay I'm
这里的功能，所以我可以说我很好
gonna connect and it'll ask me to
要连接，它会问我
connect given a locator well you saw how
给定定位器的连接，您会看到
to how that works before so I'm gonna
之前如何运作的，所以我要
say just connect and by default it'll
说只是连接，默认情况下它将
connect it's a local host 10 0 3 3 4
连接它是 localhost 10 0 3 3 4
which we already did before I could have
我们本来可以做到的
spent I stood I could say connect - -
花了我站着我可以说连接--
locator local host 10 3 3 4 by the way
定位器 localhost 10 3 3 4
this shell does it look familiar
这个外壳看起来很熟悉
you might recall from our our spring
您可能会回忆起我们的 Spring
shell spring tip video from a little
壳Spring 提示视频从一点
while back that we know these these
回来的时候，我们知道这些
capabilities these are things that you
这些都是你的能力
would get in spring shell that's because
会进入Spring Shell，这是因为
G fish the show is based on spring shell
G fish秀基于弹壳
based on the same project and in fact
基于相同的项目，实际上
you might even argue that it was birthed
您甚至可能会争辩说它诞生了
because of its need to integrate and
因为它需要整合和
support Jim fire ok so now what we want
支持吉姆，好吧，现在我们想要什么
to say list regions let's see if we can
说列表区域，让我们看看是否可以
do that nothing found yet we haven't
做那没发现的事，我们还没有
started the client either
启动客户端
let's do that so let's now run this we
让我们这样做，让我们现在运行它，我们
know that we have this thing gonna find
知道我们有这个东西会找到
the region there good it run
那里运行良好的区域
Oh what did I do wrong huh
哦，我做错了什么吧
no available servers with which to
没有可用的服务器
connect ah that's because I need the
连接啊，那是因为我需要
configuration in the property file for
在属性文件中进行配置
the client okay okay so you can't you
客户端好吧好吧，所以你不能
know same thing I there's a bit of
知道同一件事，我有一点
configuration implied here when using
使用时此处暗含的配置
the client just as we had for the server
客户端，就像我们在服务器上一样
but the configuration here also is not
但是这里的配置也不是
yet supported through the property
尚未得到酒店的支持
auto-completion
自动完成
in them in spring but-- but that will be
在 Spring ，但是-但是那将会是
that's on the way right so for our
这是正确的方式，所以对于我们
purposes it's you know not a big deal
目的是你知道没什么大不了的
it's just one simple client we say
我们说的只是一个简单的客户
sprain data gem fire dot pool dots
扭伤数据宝石火点池点
locators equals local host ten 334 look
定位器等于 localhost 的十个334外观
familiar
熟悉的
okay take two
好吧拿两个
all right that seems to have run it
好吧，似乎已经成功了
didn't stay up because there's nothing
没有熬夜，因为什么都没有
to stay up for there's no you know it's
熬夜，没有，你不知道
it's stateless right it just starts up
它是无状态的，它刚启动
and does what it does and it shuts down
并做它会关闭
there's no like web server or service
没有类似的Web服务器或服务
talk and everything it is not in point
说话，一切都不对劲
of fact a server and so we can go here
实际上是一台服务器，所以我们可以去这里
now this regions you can see that it now
现在这个地区，你现在可以看到
knows about our temperatures right so it
知道我们的温度是正确的
is clearly able to to work with our
显然能够与我们合作
temperatures which is kind of cool we
温度很酷，我们
actually also have data in there and we
实际上那里也有数据，我们
can we can run query so let's do a query
我们可以运行查询吗，让我们进行查询
query equals and it takes something
查询等于，它需要一些东西
called oql ochio is the object query
称为oql ochio是对象查询
language so i can say select count from
语言，所以我可以说从中选择计数
temps right actually just do that there
临时工实际上只是在那里做
you go 374 let's look at particular
你去了374，让我们看一下
records let's say I want to unpack the
记录说我要打开包装
ID and the city okay there we go or the
ID和城市好吗，我们去了
ID the temp rescuer and the city now
现在标识临时救援人员和城市
because it's actually first of all keep
因为它首先是保持
in mind this is just these are the Java
请记住，这就是Java
these are the records in the Java
这些是Java中的记录
database right in the Java code I didn't
我没有的Java代码中的数据库
tell anything I didn't teach gem fire or
讲任何我没有教过的宝石之火或
geode anything about our data I didn't
对我们没有的数据进行大地测量
tell it how to persist this I didn't
告诉它如何坚持我没有
even implement serializable all I did
甚至实现了我所做的可序列化
was annotate it with that region and it
用那个区域和它注释
just kind of implied the layout of this
只是暗示了这个的布局
object using reflection right this is
使用反射对象，这是
not the only way you can store data
不是存储数据的唯一方法
right you can actually use a you can see
正确，您可以实际使用
that it's working right it was first of
首先它是正确的
all working just fine
一切都很好
with this format but this isn't always
使用这种格式，但并非总是如此
the best situation suppose I wanted to
最好的情况是我想
run queries against some of the fields
针对某些字段运行查询
in a much more much much much more
在更多得多
sizable data set in that case I would
在这种情况下，我会设置大量数据
need to the the the engine the database
需要引擎数据库
platform itself and the next platform
平台本身和下一个平台
needs to unsere lies or DCO lies rather
需要不撒谎或DCO撒谎
every single temperature java object in
中的每个温度Java对象
the cache then run a test against it and
然后缓存对其进行测试，并
then result you know
然后结果你知道
it would if I want to run a condition or
如果我要运行条件或
test against just the predicate for
仅针对谓词进行测试
example I'd have to deserialize that or
例如我必须反序列化或
I do I wouldn't but the platform would
我愿意，但平台会
it would be sterilized the object do you
它会被消毒吗
reference the temperature value run
参考温度值运行
whatever query or predicate we want
我们想要的任何查询或谓词
against that temperature value and then
针对该温度值，然后
continue on right accumulating the
继续在右边积累
results into a result set that that
结果变成一个结果集
process slows things down not a huge
过程使事情变慢了
amount but it does and if you want to
数量，但确实如此，如果您想
avoid that you can there's a thing
避免你可以有事
called PD X this is a an encoding format
称为PD X，这是一种编码格式
that is proprietary to geode other data
专用于对其他数据进行大地测量
good to have a similar thing right so
拥有类似的东西是件好事
for example for using coherence they
例如使用连贯性
have something called pause POF portable
有一种叫做“暂停POF便携式”的东西
object format so it's the same idea it's
对象格式，这是相同的想法
a it's a interface it's a type
这是一个接口，它是一种类型
definition language that you define that
您定义的定义语言
is agnostic of any one particular
与任何一个特定的事物无关
language or runtime and it is basically
语言或运行时，基本上
a you basically define the layout of the
您基本上定义了
object right it's a it's a type def
正确的对象，它是一个类型def
basically if you've already done C
基本上，如果您已经做过C
you're telling it or a struct rather
你说的是一个结构
you're telling it you're telling the
你在说，你在说
runtime how memory is laid out and what
运行时如何布置内存以及什么
fields go where and you know if I look
田野去哪里，你知道我是否看
at the Third Field into the type what
在第三个字段中输入什么类型
what what can I find is it a string is a
我能找到的是一个字符串
date as an object is a boolean you know
日期作为对象是一个布尔值
etc and so that that that discussion
等，这样的讨论
that understanding helps the runtime
理解有助于运行时
because it can unpack just the one field
因为它只能解开一个领域
that you're looking for right it's not
你在寻找正确的不是
just gonna unpack this blob that is your
只是要打开这个斑点，就是你的
Java object and then and then call that
然后再调用Java对象
method based on reflection it can say oh
基于反射的方法可以说哦
you're looking for the temperature the
您正在寻找温度
the field called temperature that I
我称之为温度的领域
happen to know is a double and so thus
碰巧知道是一个双，因此
it's those less than as many bytes
那些少于字节
offset into into the payload and you can
偏移到有效载荷中，您可以
see actually behind the scenes it's
看到实际上是在幕后
cached the PDX type and it actually has
缓存了PDX类型，实际上它具有
that definition it's creating it for us
这个定义是为我们创造的
automatically but if we give it to if we
自动，但如果我们给它，如果我们
give the runtime that PDX upfront and we
提前给PDX运行时，我们
store things explicitly upfront
预先存储东西
using PDX then we get some performance
使用PDX，我们可以获得一些性能
benefits you can implement in your types
您可以在类型中实现的好处
here implemented PDX what is it writer
在这里实现了PDX是什么作家
yeah writer and then if you implement
是的作家，然后如果您实施
that you've got these methods you gather
你已经收集了这些方法
you
您
care about so I wouldn't use that you've
在乎，所以我不会用你的
also got a separate type that you would
还有一个单独的类型，你会
implement generic you know independent
实现您知道独立的通用
of any particular entity called PDX
任何称为PDX的实体
serializer or encoder or something like
序列化器或编码器或类似的东西
that it's a thing that you pass entities
这是你通过实体的事情
into and it'll it'll know how to encode
进入，它将知道如何编码
those so these are things that do this
这些就是这样做的事情
work for you normally you wouldn't
通常不会为您工作
implement all the methods you could
实现所有可能的方法
extend from a base one so extends PDX
从基础扩展，从而扩展PDX
not writer right or imp maybe right
不是作家的权利或淘气鬼也许是正确的
that's that what does that get me yeah
那是什么让我对
so you have to something like that one
所以你必须要做类似的事情
of those types right there's a there's a
在这些类型中，有一个
base one and as you can see I haven't
基地之一，如你所见，我还没有
done it recently but that works if you
最近做过，但是如果你做得到
need high performance and the benefit of
需要高性能和利益
that is that you're forced to in in in
那就是你被迫进入
in unpacking your type and explaining it
在解压您的类型并进行解释时
and articulating its structure the shape
并阐明其结构的形状
of that type to the runtime you're
该类型的运行时
forced to make concessions to the fact
被迫对事实作出让步
that this is just a bunch of bytes said
那只是一堆字节说
somewhere and and that those bytes have
某个地方，那些字节有
to be readable but when you do that you
易于阅读，但是当您这样做时
you make it possible to now then take
您现在就可以
that PDX definition that type definition
该PDX定义该类型定义
that you've explicitly defined as
您明确定义为
opposed to we've implicitly defined here
反对我们在这里隐式定义
and use that another platform so you can
并使用另一个平台，以便您可以
read that same type from that net from
从网络中读取相同类型的内容
see from signals plus whatever and
从信号加上任何东西看
there's bindings there's lots of
有约束力，有很多
different client libraries that they
他们不同的客户端库
talk to UM talk to this grid so this can
与UM交谈，与该网格交谈，这样可以
be a great intubation store if you want
如果愿意的话，成为一个很棒的插管店
to have a place where services can can
有一个可以提供服务的地方
integrate with each other they can you
他们可以互相融合
know you can have C code reading reading
知道你可以阅读C代码
the data off the sensor Hardware right
传感器硬件上的数据
and that could be writing to this to
这可能是写给
this grid and then Java code could be
这个网格，然后Java代码可能是
doing complex event processing with that
进行复杂的事件处理
data okay so let's talk about processing
数据还可以，所以我们来谈谈处理
let's talk about analytics first of all
首先让我们谈谈分析
um I would like to actually process some
嗯，我想实际处理一些
of this data I would like to be able to
这些数据我希望能够
run a query against that you can do that
针对您可以执行查询
you can create a custom finder method in
您可以在中创建自定义查找器方法
the repository it is just spring data
仓库只是Spring 数据
after all but what I would like to do is
毕竟，但我想做的是
I would like to create a custom finder
我想创建一个自定义查找器
method that that
那个方法
notified me when data is available right
数据可用时通知我
and this is a different approach than
这是不同于
perhaps you are accustomed right what I
也许你已经习惯了我
want to do here is I want the thing that
想在这里做的就是我想要的东西
I am I want the lis the data grid to
我是我想要lis数据网格
tell me when there's new data as opposed
告诉我什么时候有新数据反对
to me constantly pulling the data grid
对我而言，不断拉动数据网格
going through all the results on the
通过所有的结果
client and then finding the record that
客户，然后找到记录
matches my condition that perhaps didn't
符合我可能没有的条件
match that condition a second ago or a
再次符合该条件或
minute ago or a week ago again I've only
分钟前或一周前，我只
got a few hundred records here but it is
在这里有几百条记录，但是
not uncommon to have billions of records
拥有数十亿条记录的情况并不少见
so you know this is large-scale big big
所以你知道这是大型的
data and in the truest sense so it's a
数据，从最真实的意义上讲，
it would be inefficient and regrettable
这将是低效率的，令人遗憾的
if all you did was use Jim fire as a as
如果您所做的只是使用Jim fire作为
you might a sequel database to pull down
你可能需要续集数据库
data and process it or if you're going
数据并处理它，或者如果您要去
to treat it like a sequel database at
像对待续集数据库一样对待它
least treat it like a sequel database
至少将其视为续集数据库
and use some of the more interesting
并使用一些更有趣的
features of a sequel database right the
续集数据库的功能
equivalent of a stored procedure so what
等价于存储过程
I want to do here and so it's not even
我想在这里做，所以甚至都没有
like a stored procedure really it's a
就像存储过程一样，
more like a complex event processing
更像是复杂的事件处理
engine that happens to run like a stored
碰巧像存储引擎一样运行的引擎
procedure right what I want to say is
程序对，我想说的是
when there is a fact that is true let me
当有事实是真实的，让我
know I want the grid to be responsible
知道我要网格负责
for running a query and when there's a
用于运行查询以及何时存在
result that matches let me know but I
匹配的结果让我知道，但我
don't want to I don't want to be
不想我不想成为
bothered with constantly pulling the
困扰于不断拉
grid and having to pull data down that's
网格，不得不将数据拉下来
really inefficient the grid can run the
效率很低的网格可以运行
query for me it can it can distribute
向我查询它可以分发
the query across the grid instead of me
整个网格而不是我的查询
distributing the data across the grid
跨网格分布数据
right and so we're gonna do that we're
对，所以我们要做的是
gonna create a am a continuous query
要创建一个连续查询
okay now in order for us to have a
好的，现在我们可以
continuous query we need to you know we
连续查询，我们需要您知道我们
ended a little bit of code here not a
在这里结束了一点代码而不是
big deal gonna create a new package in
大不了的事会在
the in the client module C Q Java class
客户端模块CQ Java类中的
C Q application public static void main
CQ应用程序公共静态无效主体
string args spring application dot run
字符串args spring应用程序点运行
CQ application class args and wanna okay
CQ应用程序类args，想知道吗
so that's the skeleton of our of our
这就是我们的骨架
past to spring good application
过去到 Spring 很好的应用
naturally I want to say and they will
我自然要说，他们会
cluster configuration great
集群配置很棒
and then really we could put this
然后真的我们可以把这个
continuous query anywhere but what's
在什么地方连续查询
gonna happen is we're gonna start this
会发生的是我们要开始这个
application up we need to make sure it
应用程序，我们需要确保它
doesn't disappear so I'm gonna say new
不会消失，所以我要说新的
scanner system but in dot read isn't it
扫描仪系统，但不是点读
next isn't it yeah they go next it's
接下来不是吗，是的，他们接下来要去
gonna parse for the next token and we're
要解析下一个令牌，我们
just gonna have a continuous query here
只是要在这里连续查询
so let's add continuous query and the
因此，我们添加连续查询和
name of the query will be new
查询名称将是新的
temperature readings kind of immaterial
温度读数有点无关紧要
but nice to be precise select all from
但很高兴精确地选择所有
temps where city block contains Sam so
市区内有山姆的临时工
see what I'm doing there I'm actually
看看我在做什么我实际上在
writing a query that uses the objects
编写使用对象的查询
right it is a Java object I can say doc
正确，这是一个Java对象，我可以说doc
contains here I can do the same thing I
我在这里可以做同样的事情
can say dot substring for example zero
可以说点子字符串，例如零
three right and I get back just the
三个正确，我回来了
first three records I'm actually calling
我实际上在呼叫的前三个记录
the Java methods on string so I'm gonna
字符串上的Java方法，所以我要
say when that method gets called when
说什么时候该方法被调用
that query matches on new temperate or
该查询与新温带或
give me this EQ event and then I want to
给我这个均衡器事件，然后我想
process that I'm gonna say okay if if
我要说好的过程，如果
the event is there I'm gonna unpack it
活动在那里，我要拆包
so I'll say you know this dot get new
所以我会说你知道这个点越来越新
value and you can see I got the old
值，你可以看到我很老
value I've got the key you've got the
值，我有钥匙，你有
query that affected it any exception
查询影响它的任何异常
I've got the Delta the difference you
我让三角洲与众不同
know in bytes between the old value the
知道旧值之间的字节数
new value fella if I want you know lots
新价值的家伙，如果我想让你知道很多
of interesting information but what I
有趣的信息，但我
want is a new value and I'm gonna say if
想要是一个新的价值，我要说
present on a map it
在地图上显示它
to a temperature all right I'm gonna say
到一个好的温度我要说
Tim and I'll just print it out okay so
蒂姆，我会把它打印出来好
system odd temp got to string and of
系统奇数温度已达到且
course this could be CQ event very good
当然这可能是CQ活动
all right so there's my CQ method so
好的，这是我的CQ方法
basically whenever there's a fact that
基本上只要有事实
matches this query
符合此查询
whenever there's a record that's been
每当有记录
written into the Navis that matches this
写入与此匹配的Navis
query this method will get called and
查询此方法将被调用
I'll get a chance to process it right I
我将有机会正确处理它
can write it out I can do interesting
可以写出来我可以做有趣的事
things with that so so now I've got the
这样的事情，所以现在我有了
CQ application I've got the client let's
客户服务的CQ应用程序
go ahead and run this okay we'll run
继续并运行此行，我们将运行
this code and we'll see then that should
此代码，我们将看到那应该
hopefully stay awake and nothing will
希望保持清醒，什么都不会
happen when it starts it will just sit
发生在它开始时会坐
there sort of wait for input or or wait
有某种等待输入或或等待
for something to write down to the
写下一些东西给
output one hopes okay good so there's
输出一个希望好吧，所以有
that now let's go to our client and run
现在让我们去我们的客户并运行
the application again and I'm going to
再次申请，我要
quickly switch back to the CQ
快速切换回CQ
application once this is up and running
一旦启动并运行
so we're in the CQ application it says
所以我们在CQ应用程序中说
started seek application there we go you
开始寻找应用程序，我们去你那里
can see that you know almost immediately
可以看到你几乎立即知道
all those rights that I've just done in
我刚刚完成的所有这些权利
the other thread in a client application
客户端应用程序中的另一个线程
and the other process that matched Sam
和匹配Sam的其他过程
and you know there's a few of them in
而且你知道其中有一些
there in our data set are returned
在我们的数据集中返回
immediately right instantly it takes no
立即马上就不需要
time at all and that would be true where
根本没有时间，那在哪里
are we running on a thousand nodes or
我们是在一千个节点上运行还是
just one note as I am in this in this
就像我在此的一个音符
instance right so that's pretty cool huh
实例正确，所以很酷吧
I like that I mean I love continues
我喜欢我，我爱继续
created to think it you can use it for
创建以为您可以将其用于
pub/sub kind of things you can say okay
pub / sub之类的事情你可以说还可以
I'm interested in any new messages well
我对任何新消息都很感兴趣
what does that mean well give me a
这意味着什么给我一个
continuous query that selects all four
选择全部四个的连续查询
messages it doesn't get simpler than
消息没有比这更简单的了
that right notify me when there's a new
有新消息时，通知我
message what about a new message in the
消息中的新消息呢
chat
聊天室
okay just select all from from chats
好吧，从聊天中全选
where you know session ID equals that
您知道会话ID等于
whatever you can do all sorts of very
不管你能做什么，
interesting things here okay I'll I uh I
有趣的事情，好吧，我会，我
like that but what if I wanted something
这样，但是如果我想要一些东西
that I couldn't really articulate with G
我无法真正与G表达
with oql right oql is the object query
与oql对，oql是对象查询
language I like the object we're langage
语言我喜欢我们的语言对象
but a lot of times I need to do custom
但是很多时候我需要做定制
processing on the data and here to geode
处理数据并在此处进行大地测量
comes into
进入
because if you want to do something with
因为如果你想做点什么
Java code in a sequel data store or
后续数据存储中的Java代码或
MongoDB or anything like this you have
MongoDB或类似的东西
to pull the data in some memory you have
将数据提取到您拥有的某些内存中
to pull it into the client and then
将其拉入客户端，然后
profit you know stream through the data
您知道从数据流中获利
in the client and you can't you know
在客户中，你不知道
unless you go out of your way to to
除非您竭尽所能
bring in threads and so on you can't
引入线程等等，你不能
really parallel eyes any of that work
真正平行的眼睛
and certainly if any of that work is i/o
当然可以肯定，如果其中任何一项工作是我/我
bound you're not gonna be able to scale
一定你无法扩展
that up you know infinitely certainly
你肯定无限地知道
you're not going to scale it up on a
你不会在一个
single node a single instance so now you
单节点单个实例，所以现在您
have to get into the business of trying
必须涉足尝试
to parallelize it across different nodes
使其在不同节点之间并行化
and sure there are technologies like
并确定有类似的技术
spring batch remote chunking that
Spring批处理远程分块
supports this but again now you're in a
支持这一点，但现在又在
whole different paradigm what I would
完全不同的范式
like to do is to say here's some
我想说的是
functionality for processing I would
处理功能，我会
like to do please run the processing
喜欢做的请运行处理
logic across all the regions in my
我所有地区的逻辑
system okay and and this is what we can
系统还可以，这就是我们可以做到的
do with custom functions ok these
使用自定义功能好这些
functions they can do some very
他们可以做一些非常有用的功能
interesting things they can do some very
他们可以做一些非常有趣的事情
interesting things that you might not
有趣的事情，你可能不会
you might not have thought about like
你可能没有想过
for example one example is let's suppose
例如，假设一个例子
you've got a bunch of CSV files this is
您有一堆CSV文件，这是
a common example that you know some
你知道一些常见的例子
people have and you know for did data
人们有，你知道有数据吗
ingest they want to load a whole bunch
摄取他们想要装载一大堆
of records into the memory and then
记录到内存中，然后
process it or you know analyze it it's
处理它，或者您知道分析它是
one but they need to load the data the
一个，但他们需要加载数据
ingest itself is tedious well suppose I
假设我摄取本身很乏味
had a cluster with each node in the
在每个节点中都有一个群集
cloud platform and by the way cloud
云平台和顺便说一下云
technologies are great for this because
技术对此非常有用，因为
they can this thing can scale out
他们可以扩展这个东西
horizontally and infinite and
水平无限
dynamically right so if you're using
动态正确，所以如果您使用
something like PCC the pivotal cloud
像PCC这样的关键云
cache on Cloud Foundry then that's just
缓存在Cloud Foundry上，那只是
a no-brainer you just deploy it and you
轻而易举的事，您只需部署它，然后您
can talk to it from any of a number of
可以从许多
your different nodes if you're on an i
您在i上的不同节点
as platform something like at AWS or GCP
作为平台，例如AWS或GCP
or as who are of course also great
或者说谁当然也很棒
choices I mean and there is let's
我的意思是选择，让我们
suppose you had such a deployment center
假设您有这样一个部署中心
to put topology each node each virtual
为每个虚拟节点放置拓扑
machine on the I ass might for example
例如，机器上的屁股
be connected to shared storage right you
可以连接到共享存储
have a e you have a amount where you can
有一个你有你可以的数量
read data you've got batch data CSV data
读取您具有批处理数据CSV数据的数据
whatever each region you you know you
无论您认识每个区域
can actually write to the grid
可以实际写入网格
a whole bunch of keys and the keys could
一堆钥匙，钥匙可以
be just keys and then empty values and
只是键，然后是空值，
then you could run the processing and
然后您可以运行处理程序并
that'll be fairly distributed across all
将会公平地分布在所有
the nodes in the cluster right so it
集群中的节点正确
won't just be on one node it'll be load
不仅会在一个节点上，还会被加载
balanced and if you want by the way you
平衡，如果您想通过方式
can specify redundancy you can say for
可以指定您可以说的冗余
this node please replicate it to this
这个节点请复制到这个
other node right for example or you know
例如其他节点权利，或者您知道
you you specify that you want replicated
您指定要复制
number of different times you can even
您可以连连的不同时间数
get transactions right you can actually
正确进行交易
get access to the data store to say I
可以访问数据存储说我
insist on being able to roll this back a
坚持要能够回滚
something goes wrong there's even
出问题了，甚至
support for JTA in geode I mean it's got
在geode中支持JTA，我的意思是
everything it really is just a
一切真的只是一个
enterprise-e
企业
well-thought-out thing you know I
你深思熟虑的东西我
wouldn't use DTA but if you need to the
不会使用DTA，但是如果您需要
point is this is one of those things you
关键是这是你的那些事之一
can use it with you could use it with
可以和你一起使用
that and for example JMS or or whatever
那，例如JMS或其他
right but and it also has logical
对，但是它也有逻辑
resource local transactions that's the
资源本地交易是
other thing you can do multiple writes
你可以做多次写的另一件事
and then concurrently I started turns
然后我同时开始转弯
actually write them or roll them back I
实际写或回滚我
mean these are all sort of beyond the
意味着这些都超出了
scope of what we're going to talk about
我们要谈论的范围
here today but you can also insist that
今天在这里，但你也可以坚持
when I write I insist on having a
我写的时候坚持要
guarantee that it's been replicated
保证已被复制
across one or two or three or five or n
跨越一或两个或三个或五个或n
or you know some other strategy that you
或者你知道其他一些策略
arrive at whatever strategy arrived at
达成任何策略
for determining how many other nodes you
用于确定您还有多少个其他节点
can insist on achieving that minimum
可以坚持达到最低要求
sort of a replication set okay so yeah
某种复制集好吧，是的
like that better is one of the really
像这样更好是真正的
really compelling features of of TOD now
现在TOD真正引人注目的功能
I want to run a function and if I had
我想运行一个函数，如果我有
this data ingest scenario I could for
我可以针对这种数据提取方案
example insert a bunch of keys into the
示例将一堆钥匙插入
cut into the cluster and then I could
切入群集，然后我可以
run this function that visited each node
运行访问每个节点的此功能
in the cluster and then I could look up
在集群中，然后我可以查找
my current I could find all the keys
我目前能找到所有的钥匙
that use that a current node on which
使用该节点上的当前节点
the function is executing as the lead
该功能正在执行
node as the master node as the the node
节点作为主节点
on which this write was first written
最初写此写的内容
right there's other nodes there's a
右边还有其他节点
there's secondary nodes that have the
有具有
right as well there's a replication
正确的还有复制
nodes but this is the leader node right
节点，但这是领导节点
I can write to
我可以写信给
all of these different leader nodes and
所有这些不同的领导者节点和
I can run the function I can say if I am
我可以运行我可以说的功能
the leader node for a given right
给定权限的领导节点
I want to process the keys that were in
我想处理其中的钥匙
that right and I would then weed in my
那个权利，然后我会除草
function on that node all the CSV files
在该节点上运行所有CSV文件
that match the keys that are resident on
与驻留在其中的键匹配
that node and no more and that way I
该节点，仅此而已
would be charged with you know I would
会被指控你知道我会
read whatever CSV files I need to read
读取我需要读取的任何CSV文件
on one node and all the other nodes
在一个节点上，在所有其他节点上
would read the CSV files that are
会读取CSV文件
resident to that node and that way it be
驻留在那个节点上，这样
parallelized and I could just invoke
并行化，我可以调用
this function once from the client and
此功能一次来自客户端
the work that has farmed out across you
遍布你的工作
know n nodes in the cluster could be -
知道群集中的n个节点可能是-
it could be a thousand right you can
可能一千个就可以
parallel s just any kind of work like
并行可以做任何类似的工作
this so you get nice logical
这样你就很合乎逻辑
distribution even if you're not even if
分布，即使你不是
the even if you're not concerned with
即使您不关心
just data sharding if you just want a
如果您只想要一个数据分片
fair scheduler this is a really
公平的调度程序，这真的是
interesting thing to have so let's write
有趣的事情，让我们写
a simple function not nothing quite so
一个简单的功能不是什么都没有
complicated as what I've just just
就像我刚才所说的那样复杂
articulated but yeah interesting in of
明确表达，但有趣的是
itself okay so what we're just going to
本身还可以，所以我们要做的是
write a function we have to create a
写一个函数，我们必须创建一个
client side view of that function okay
该功能的客户端视图还可以
so when I say average temperature
所以当我说平均温度
function okay
功能还可以
invoker I I don't you can call what do
调用者II不，你可以叫做什么
you want it's just an interface right
您希望它只是一个接口就对了
very very spring data ish right I'm
我非常非常 Spring 的数据
gonna say I want to run this function on
要说我想在
the region called temps we didn't call
我们没有打电话到的叫temps的地区
the temps all right and it would be nice
暂时没事，那就太好了
if you spilled this quickly
如果你很快把它洒了
I clearly am not capable of that but you
我显然没有能力，但是你
don't actually have to I just know
其实我不必知道
there's no importance no no no
不重要不不不
importance is placed on the name of the
重要性放在名称上
interface itself that is not true
接口本身不正确
however for the name of the function I
但是对于函数的名称我
think we can just do this I think we can
认为我们可以做到这一点，我认为我们可以
say double average temperature okay
说双倍平均温度还可以
let's try that so that's the name of the
让我们尝试一下，这就是
function and we have to define that
功能，我们必须定义
function in the client so actually
在客户端起作用，所以实际上
before we owe and rather in the server
在欠我们之前，而是在服务器中
but before we do that let's let's inject
但在我们这样做之前，让我们先注入
that code and get that working so
该代码并使其正常工作
private final average temperature
私人最终平均气温
invoker
调用者
I'll call it invoker add the arguments
我称它为调用者添加参数
and here invoke function I wanna say dot
在这里调用函数我想说点
average temperature and that should
平均温度，那应该
visit each region and calculate the
参观每个地区并计算
average of all the temperatures in that
所有温度的平均值
region and nowhere else and then from
地区和其他地方，然后从
there I am going to visit each
我要去那里参观
temperature there and calculate average
那里的温度并计算平均值
so average to double and I'll just say x
所以平均要翻倍，我只说x
equals x it's an identity function and
等于x这是一个恒等函数，
average lustre average alright and we
平均光泽平均好吧，我们
just write that out I may use Lombok
写下我可以使用龙目岛
Here I am nothing nothing if not lazy
在这里我什么都不是什么都不懒
it's all say log dot info cluster
都是说日志点信息集群
average and what all right there's my
平均，还好我的
cluster average temperature okay so we
集群平均温度好，所以我们
now we need to write the processing code
现在我们需要编写处理代码
and as you can imagine our function is
您可以想象我们的功能是
gonna look for any similar to this ok
会寻找与此相似的东西
but we didn't I hate to spoil the plot
但是我们不讨厌破坏剧情
you might I might have extracted this
你可能我可能已经提取了这个
out into a common method that is shared
变成共享的通用方法
between client and server but um you
在客户端和服务器之间，但是你呢
know that's cool I'm okay I'm okay I'm
知道那很酷，我很好，我很好，我
happy leaving it like that so let's now
高兴地离开它，所以让我们现在
go back to our server
回到我们的服务器
alright and in the server code in the
好吧，在服务器代码中
first things first we need to tell the
首先，我们需要告诉
locator about the function so we're
关于功能的定位器，所以我们
gonna do that by creating the function
通过创建函数来做到这一点
and the function will be in a place that
该功能将放置在
is in the server
在服务器中
okay and we're just gonna implement the
好的，我们将实施
function it's gonna be called average
函数将被称为平均值
temperature function in for example it
例如温度功能
doesn't have to be called it I mean it
不必叫它我的意思是
could be called whatever you want really
可以叫你真正想要的
it's just a spring beam at component and
它只是组件上的Spring 梁
it's going to be a gem fire function
这将是一个宝石射击功能
public void calculate average or no it's
公共无效计算平均值或否
average temperatures in it it's this
这是平均温度
just method here and I'm gonna inject
只是这里的方法，我要注入
the region data it's gonna be a map of
区域数据将是
string to temperature okay there's the
串到温度好吧
data and I need to tell my locator about
数据，我需要告诉我的定位器
that so I'll say that this is a it's
所以我会说这是一个
gonna have to do a component scan
将不得不进行组件扫描
looking in there okay and redundantly I
看着那里好吧，多余的我
think I'm being redundant here but just
认为我在这里很多余，但是
in case pretty sure you don't need that
以防万一你肯定不需要
okay so there's my my components can
好，所以我的组件可以
there and do we need the same thing on
在那里，我们是否需要同样的东西
the server we might need the same thing
服务器，我们可能需要同样的东西
in the server I'm not a hundred percent
在服务器上我不是百分之一百
sure but I think we're okay for now
当然可以，但我认为我们现在还可以
let's go ahead and just leave it out for
让我们继续前进，将其保留
now um yeah that should be okay that
现在，嗯，应该没关系
should be fine so let's let's try that
应该很好，让我们尝试一下
that's the function that's the locator
这就是定位器的功能
okay so we've got that
好，所以我们知道了
go ahead and go ahead and restart the
继续前进，然后重新启动
locator itself and actually you know
定位器本身，实际上你知道
before I do that I should implement this
在我这样做之前，我应该先实现
so I'll say data dot values dot stream
所以我说数据点值点流
dot map temperature get temperature and
点图温度获取温度和
I'll say I want to get the doubles so
我会说我想得到双打
averages for all the data in this
此所有数据的平均值
current region right in the current node
当前节点中的当前区域
I'm processing on so I'm gonna get all
我正在处理，所以我会得到所有
the data from there I'm gonna collect it
我要从那里收集数据
so actually I don't know that don't want
所以实际上我不知道不要
to say dot map doc collect average to
说点地图文档将平均值收集到
double X X identity right same as before
双XX身份与以前相同
average okay and we was dumb luck here
一般还好，我们在这里很傻
so log4j and I'm gonna say log got info
所以log4j，我要说日志有信息
arrived at average
平均到达
average okay and then we're just gonna
一般还可以，然后我们就
return the result turn average I think I
返回结果转弯平均值我想我
need the return type that makes sense as
需要有意义的返回类型
close and you don't want to return type
关闭并且您不想返回类型
I suppose I do it I want the double and
我想我要加倍
that double is gonna be the average
那两倍将是平均值
already okay that looks good
已经可以了，看起来不错
I think we can leave it there now yeah
我想我们可以现在就把它留在那里
that's very straightforward let's just
这很简单，让我们
leave that there and we've got the
离开那边，我们得到了
little log statement to confirm that we
小日志声明，以确认我们
visited this node so we can actually see
拜访了这个节点，所以我们实际上可以看到
the work fan-out as we care as we want
工作随心所欲
to so we start this that's for locator
所以我们从定位器开始
or we start that first we need a locator
否则我们首先需要一个定位器
oh I did it again didn't I
哦，我又做了一次，不是吗
renamed ever Ridge
改名为Ever Ridge
okay that's fine and then the server we
好的，那很好，然后我们的服务器
start that
开始那个
okay let's go back to G fish just to
好吧，让我们回到G鱼
confirm everything's as we expect so
确认一切如我们所愿
I'll do connect by default good list
我会默认连接好列表
functions
职能
there's our average temperature function
这是我们的平均温度函数
oh it's in there twice average
哦，那是平均水平的两倍
temperature function delete remove no
温度功能删除删除否
region temps no that's number one - I
地区临时工不是第一位-我
mean there we go we've got that
就是说我们去那里了
hey I mean
嘿，我的意思是
should be fine I don't know I didn't
应该很好我不知道我没有
we'll be okay okay let's see what
我们会没事的，让我们看看
happens so that's this you know we can
发生的就是这样，你知道我们可以
actually make it a little bit simpler so
实际上使它更简单一点
let's just so that we know we're on the
只是为了让我们知道我们在
same page this would be the app it'll be
在同一页面上，它将是应用程序
called average we're just gonna call it
叫做平均值，我们将称之为
average okay very very boring but that
平均还可以，非常无聊，但是
way we know is happening so let me
我们知道发生的方式，所以让我
rewrite that and when we start the
重写它，当我们开始
client
客户
we start
我们开始
all right so we've got the average
好的，所以我们得到了平均值
that's the client application returned
那是客户端应用程序返回
this or run this
这个或运行这个
alright whoops
好的呐喊
right the function is not registered
右功能未注册
fair enough let's go back over here and
公平地说，让我们回到这里，
restart the locator
重新启动定位器
good server
好的服务器
okay and now if we go to list we're
好吧，现在，如果我们去列表，我们是
going to connect this functions there's
要连接此功能，有
our function average
我们的平均功能
oh it's knit twice okay so that actually
哦，编织两次就可以了
does that has the effect okay so there's
这样做效果还好吗，所以
that and then we go back to our client
然后我们回到客户那里
client application and hopefully this
客户应用程序，希望这
will work I'm not sure about to return
可以工作，我不确定要回来
objects from the function invoker or if
来自函数调用程序的对象，或者
it can be downcast like this but uh
可以像这样沮丧
we'll see
我们拭目以待
worst case alright that seems okay did
最坏的情况似乎还可以
we get the results back to be even
我们得到的结果是均匀的
bother client application cluster
困扰客户应用程序集群
average look at that point four nine so
平均看那一点四点九点
that's that invoked the the reads
那就是调用读取
accounted in did the calculation across
计入了计算
the cluster we can confirm that by
我们可以通过
arrived at average blah blah blah on
到达平均等等等等
this one server node so again if we had
这个服务器节点，如果我们有
more than one node we'd see that printed
我们将看到多个节点打印出来
out at every single instant alright my
每一刻都好
friends we've only begun to scratch the
朋友，我们才刚刚开始
surface I hope you you can appreciate
希望你能体会到
some of the opportunities here we didn't
我们没有的一些机会
even look at the cache manager we didn't
甚至看我们没有的缓存管理器
even look at the basic key value store
甚至看基本的键值存储
I feel like treating gem fire geode as
我觉得就像把宝石火geode当作
just a regular key value stores it's a
只是一个常规的键值存储它是一个
bit misguided you're really missing out
误入歧途，您真的错过了
on some of the most one of the most high
在一些最高的
speed one was scalable systems in the
速度之一是
world so hopefully you've gotten
世界如此希望你已经
something out of this journey thank you
旅途中有些事谢谢
so much for watching and as always we'll
这么多的观看，我们将一如既往
see you next time
下次见
you
您